Kumar Shubham

Full Stack Developer (Sr. Software Engineer)

#669 SF, Sec 77
Mohali, Punjab, India
(+91) 97793-08242
shubham.it.chd@gmail.com
https://www.shubhamit.com

Summary

I am a senior Full Stack developer of around 5 years in building high-quality websites. I am comfortable with ASP.NET, Angular, .Net Core, MS SQL, Web API, C#, Typescript, Entity Framework, LINQ, and DBMS technology using Microsoft SQL Server, SQL Injection, Stored Procedures. I am a good client handler with an effective understanding of the actual requirements of the project with output as the client's needs. I'm a quick learner and tackle complex code quite easily.

EXPERIENCE

FIS, Quark City, Sec 79, Mohali — *Sr. Software Engineer*April 2018 - Present

FIS is the world's largest global provider dedicated to financial technology solutions. FIS empowers the financial world with software, services, consulting and outsourcing solutions focused on retail and institutional banking, payments, asset and wealth management, risk and compliance, trade enablement, transaction processing and record-keeping. FIS' more than 52,000 worldwide employees are passionate about moving our clients' business forward.

JnG IT Solutions, F 355, 8 B, Mohali — Sr. Software Engineer

July 2015 - April 2018

It's a software development company which provides custom services to clients and mainly focuses on the development of parcel delivery services.

EDUCATION

R.S.D College (Aff. P.U.), Ferozepur, Punjab— *B.C.A with 68%* April 2013 - April 2015

Dashmesh Public School (Aff. PSEB), Ferozepur, Punjab—12th with 73%

April 2011 - March 2012

S.B.S. Public School (Aff. PSEB), Ferozepur, Punjab— 10th with 68%

April 2009 - March 2010

SKILLS

- C#
- Angular
- Asp.Net
- .Net Core
- Web API, Web Service
- REST, GraphQL
- ADO.NET, EF
- SQL
- JQuery
- HTML, CSS
- Material Design, Flex
- .Net Design Patterns
- Git, BitBucket

LANGUAGES

- English
- Hindi
- Punjabi

Awards

MAD (Make a Difference)
-FIS

PROJECTS

Online Banking

This is a banking domain project. This is a FIS product and used by around 800 clients. This project provides facilities like transfer, ACH, Wire etc. I worked on a messaging and transfer module of this project.

Team Size	50
Languages and Tools	ASP.NET API 2, SQL SERVER 2014, Angular 6, Material Design and Flex

4InShip

4InShip is a premiere United States based parcel forwarding service company connecting international customers with American goods. It will consolidate your packages in a beastly way so that it will cost you quite less according to your original packages cost.

Team Size	2
Languages and Tools	ASP.NET MVC 5, SQL SERVER 2008 R2, Entity Framework, LINQ, Javascript, JQuery, CSS

SZGMC

SZGMC stands for Sheikh Zayed Grand Mosque Center. It is a **World's 6th largest mosque**. Any person who is keen to visit the center needs to register a tour on the website by himself or through the tour operator. It is the world's second most prominent architectural pioneer.

Team Size	4
Languages and Tools	ASP.NET MVC 5, SQL SERVER 2008 R2, Entity Framework, LINQ, Javascript, JQuery, CSS

Courierpoint

Courierpoint provides branded courier services to thousands of businesses, online stores and individuals throughout the UK.It offers a platform that allows you to compare the different couriers. It is a product of my first Company.It's easy to compare different courier prices and choose the best service.

Team Size	2
Languages and Tools	ASP.NET Web Forms SQL SERVER 2008 R2, Entity Framework, LINQ, Javascript, JQuery, CSS

MadcityHomes

Madcity Homes is Madison's #1 Flat Fee MLS and For Sale By Owner Listing Company. This is basically a housing domain where we can find our dream home.

Team Size	1
Languages and Tools	ASP.NET MVC 5, SQL SERVER 2008 R2, Entity Framework, LINQ, Javascript, JQuery, CSS

Kumar Shubham